Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Audio Visual Material
  - Books
    - Sponsor: the Magazine of Broadcast Advertising, May 16, 1966- NBC 40th Anniversary Issue –2 copies (Box 141, Folder 5.)
    - Television/Radio Age – NBC 50th Anniversary, 1926 - 1976 (Box 141, Folder 6.)